University of Connecticut 1998.0185
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1935-1962
  - 1954-1955
    - National Science Foundation (Box 9:, Folder 43)
    - Navy (Box 9:, Folder 44)
    - N. E. Association Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 9:, Folder 45)
    - N. E. Land Grant Colleges (Box 9:, Folder 46)
    - New Positions (Box 9:, Folder 47)
    - News Coordinator - Charles Niles (Box 9:, Folder 48)
    - New York State Registration Statement - Charitable organization (Box 9:, Folder 49)
    - Noank Lobster Hatchery (Box 9:, Folder 50)
    - Northby, Arwood S. - Director student personnel (Box 9:, Folder 51)
    - O (Box 9:, Folder 52)
    - P (Box 9:, Folder 53)
    - Paul, George S. - Director, Labor Management (Box 9:, Folder 54)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 9:, Folder 55)
    - Philippine contract (Box 9:, Folder 56)
      - Physical Sciences Building (Box 10:, Folder 1)
      - Poultry Science Building (Box 10:, Folder 2)
      - Powers, John - Guidance and Placement (Box 10:, Folder 3)
      - Problems facing higher education (Box 10:, Folder 4)
      - Public Works Department - T. J. Murphy (Box 10:, Folder 5)
    - Q (Box 10:, Folder 6)
    - R (Box 10:, Folder 7)
    - Re (Box 10:, Folder 8)
    - Research corporation (Box 10:, Folder 9)
    - Research foundation (Box 10:, Folder 10)
    - Research Grants (Box 10:, Folder 11)
    - Resolutions (Box 10:, Folder 12)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. - Governor of Connecticut (Box 10:, Folder 13)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. - University Comptroller (Box 10:, Folder 14)
    - Rising tide of school and college enrollment (Box 10:, Folder 15)
    - Ro (Box 10:, Folder 16)
    - Room and board rates (Box 10:, Folder 17)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 10:, Folder 18)
    - S (Box 10:, Folder 19)
    - Scholarships and gifts (Box 10:, Folder 20)
    - Seventy - fifth anniversary (Box 10:, Folder 21)
    - Seventy - fifth Committee acceptance (Box 10:, Folder 22)
    - Shippee, Lester E. - Chr. Of the Board, 1954-1955 (Box 10:, Folder 23)
    - Sm (Box 10:, Folder 24)
    - Student Senate finance, Problems of (Box 10:, Folder 25)
    - State universities (Box 10:, Folder 26)
    - Sti (Box 10:, Folder 27)
    - Student Senate - Earl Capuano, president (Box 10:, Folder 28)
    - Suisman, Edward A. (Trustee) (Box 10:, Folder 29)
    - Surveys (Box 10:, Folder 30)
    - T (Box 10:, Folder 31)
    - Tappan, Frances - Tech. Director Physical Therapy (Box 10:, Folder 32)
    - Teich, Frederic C. (Box 10:, Folder 33)
    - To (Box 10:, Folder 34)
    - Trecker, Harleigh - Dean, Social Work (Box 10:, Folder 35)
    - T.V. (Box 10:, Folder 36)
    - U (Box 10:, Folder 37)
    - Union board and building - Max Andrews (Box 10:, Folder 38)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 10:, Folder 39)
    - U.S. Office of Health, Education - Oveta C. Hobby, Education - S. M. Brownell (Box 10:, Folder 40)
    - University Commercials (Box 10:, Folder 41)
    - University Scholars (Box 10:, Folder 42)
    - University Senate (Box 10:, Folder 43)
    - V (Box 10:, Folder 44)
    - Van Bibber, E. George - Dir. Physical Education (Box 10:, Folder 45)
    - W (Box 10:, Folder 46)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 10:, Folder 47)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 10:, Folder 48)
    - Westcott and Mapes (Box 10:, Folder 49)
    - Wh (Box 10:, Folder 50)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean, Graduate School (Box 10:, Folder 51)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, Nursing (Box 10:, Folder 52)
    - Wi (Box 10:, Folder 53)
    - Wo (Box 10:, Folder 54)
    - Young, W. B. “Sponsorship of Agricultural Extension” (Box 10:, Folder 55)
    - Young, W.B. - Dean of Agriculture (Box 10:, Folder 56)
  - 1955-1956
    - A (Box 11:, Folder 1)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean of Business Adm (Box 11:, Folder 2)
    - Administrative report (Box 11:, Folder 3)
    - American Council on Education (Box 11:, Folder 4)
    - American Council on Education - National Scholarship Program (Box 11:, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1955-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 6)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences - Meeting (Box 11:, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General (state) (Box 11:, Folder 8)
    - Bailey, Clark L. (Box 11:, Folder 9)
    - Be (Box 11:, Folder 10)
    - Belden, L. Richard (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 11)
    - Bequests (Box 11:, Folder 12)
    - Bi (Box 11:, Folder 13)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 14)
    - Board material (Box 11:, Folder 15)
    - Board of Trustees - special finance committee (Box 11:, Folder 16)
    - Br (Box 11:, Folder 17)
    - Brammell, P. Roay - Dean, School of Education (Box 11:, Folder 18)
    - Brock, C. Ray (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 19)
    - Budget (Box 11:, Folder 20)
    - Budget division, State (Box 11:, Folder 21)
    - Campus (Box 11:, Folder 22)
    - Capital outlay (Box 11:, Folder 23)
    - Carter, W. H. - Dean, Arts and Sciences Coordinator National Defense (Box 11:, Folder 24)
    - Christian, J. O. - Director, Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 11:, Folder 25)
    - Co (Box 11:, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's housing (Box 11:, Folder 27)
    - Commencement, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 28)
    - Committee letters (Box 11:, Folder 29)
    - Conferences (Box 11:, Folder 30)
    - Congress (Box 11:, Folder 31)
    - Conn. Committee on Food, Drugs and Devices (Box 11:, Folder 32)
    - Contracts (Box 11:, Folder 33)
    - Cr (Box 11:, Folder 34)
    - D (Box 11:, Folder 35)
    - Deans and directors (Box 11:, Folder 36)
    - Do (Box 11:, Folder 37)
    - Dudley, George C. (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 38)
    - Eddy, Edward D., Jr. (Box 11:, Folder 39)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 11:, Folder 40)
    - Engleman, Finis - Commissioner of Education (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 41)
    - Expansion of facilities (Box 11:, Folder 42)
    - F (Box 11:, Folder 43)
    - Fees, a Study of College (Box 11:, Folder 44)
    - Finance Commissioner - Joseph M. Loughlin (Box 11:, Folder 45)
    - Fo (Box 11:, Folder 46)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 11:, Folder 47)
    - Fraternities and sororities, 1955-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 48)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 49)
    - Ge (Box 11:, Folder 50)
    - Gi (Box 11:, Folder 51)
    - Gill, Joseph N. - Commissioner of Agriculture (Trustee) (Box 11:, Folder 52)
    - Gleason, John H. - Director of Division of Communications (Box 11:, Folder 53)
    - Goodchild, Franklin M. - Director, Division of Univ. Health (Box 11:, Folder 54)
    - Gr (Box 11:, Folder 55)
    - H (Box 11:, Folder 56)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 11:, Folder 57)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 11:, Folder 58)
    - Husky Network (Box 11:, Folder 59)
    - I (Box 11:, Folder 60)
    - IBM Contract (Box 11:, Folder 61)
    - J (Box 11:, Folder 62)
    - Joint Advisory Panel on ROTC affairs - Lt. Col. Schmidt (Box 11:, Folder 63)
    - K (Box 11:, Folder 64)
    - L (Box 11:, Folder 65)
    - Land Grant College Association - Executive Committee (Box 12:, Folder 1)
    - Land Grant Study (Box 12:, Folder 2)
    - Langrock, David T. (Box 12:, Folder 3)
    - Leaves, sabbaticals and otherwise (Box 12:, Folder 4)
    - Letters of recommendation (Box 12:, Folder 5)
    - Liaison Committee - Board of Trustees and State Department of Education (Box 12:, Folder 6)
    - M (Box 12:, Folder 7)
    - Mackie, Helen (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 8)
    - Mahoney, Mary H. (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 9)
    - Manning, Stuart - Acting co - director, Univ. Extension (Box 12:, Folder 10)
    - Map (Box 12:, Folder 11)
    - Marsh, E. Lea, Jr. (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 12)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, Home Economics (Box 12:, Folder 13)
    - McH (Box 12:, Folder 14)
    - Me (Box 12:, Folder 15)
    - Medical dental veterinary (Box 12:, Folder 16)
    - Mi (Box 12:, Folder 17)
    - Military Day (Box 12:, Folder 18)
    - Military department - Col. Horace B. Frederick (Box 12:, Folder 19)
    - Milk Vending Machines (Box 12:, Folder 20)
    - Mo (Box 12:, Folder 21)
    - Moyle, Wallace A. (Box 12:, Folder 22)
    - N (Box 12:, Folder 23)
    - Naming of new buildings (Box 12:, Folder 24)
    - National Council on Accrediting, 1955-1956 (Box 12:, Folder 25)
    - New Buildings (Box 12:, Folder 26)
    - Newburn, Harry K. - Educational Television and Radio Center (Box 12:, Folder 27)
    - New England Land Grant Colleges (Box 12:, Folder 28)
    - New positions (Box 12:, Folder 29)
    - Northby, Arwood S. - Director, Division of Student Personnel (Box 12:, Folder 30)
    - Nuclear Reactor Project Proposal (Box 12A:, Folder 1)
    - O (Box 12:, Folder 31)
    - P (Box 12:, Folder 32)
    - Pictures (Box 12:, Folder 33)
    - Paul, George - Dir., Institute of Labor Management (Box 12:, Folder 34)
    - Physical Sciences Building (Box 12:, Folder 35)
    - Pl (Box 12:, Folder 36)
    - Powers, John E. (Box 12:, Folder 37)
    - Projects (Box 12:, Folder 38)
    - Public Works Department - Timothy J. Murphy, Jr. (Box 12:, Folder 39)
    - Q (Box 12:, Folder 40)
    - R (Box 12:, Folder 41)
    - Re (Box 12:, Folder 42)
    - Research Corporation (Box 12:, Folder 43)
    - Research Grants (Box 12:, Folder 44)
    - Resolutions (Box 12:, Folder 45)
    - Ribicoff, A. A. - Governor (Box 12:, Folder 46)
    - Riccio, L. C. - University Comptroller (Box 12:, Folder 47)
    - Ro (Box 12:, Folder 48)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 49)
    - S (Box 12:, Folder 50)
    - Sch (Box 12:, Folder 51)
    - Schaffer, Beldon H. - Acting Director, Institutes of Public Service (Box 12:, Folder 52)
    - Schneller, Richard F. (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 53)
    - Science talent award winners (Box 12:, Folder 54)
    - Se (Box 12:, Folder 55)
    - Service and research facilities (Box 12:, Folder 56)
    - Seventy - fifth anniversary (Box 12:, Folder 57)
    - Sh (Box 12:, Folder 58)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (Trustee) (Box 12:, Folder 59)
    - Si (Box 12:, Folder 60)
    - Sistare, Willard M. (Box 12:, Folder 61)
    - Sm (Box 12:, Folder 62)
    - Speeches (Box 12:, Folder 63)
    - Spielman, Arless A. - Asst. Dir. Agrl. Experiment (Box 12:, Folder 64)
    - State Building Program Commission (Box 12:, Folder 65)
    - State Universities Association (Box 12:, Folder 66)
    - Student Senate, 1955-1956 (Box 13:, Folder 1)
    - Su (Box 13:, Folder 2)
    - Suisman, Edward A. (Trustee) (Box 13:, Folder 3)
    - T (Box 13:, Folder 4)
    - Tappan, Frances - Tech. Dir. School of Physical Therapy (Box 13:, Folder 5)
    - T.V. (Box 13:, Folder 6)
    - To (Box 13:, Folder 7)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Box 13:, Folder 8)
    - U (Box 13:, Folder 9)
    - Union board and building (Box 13:, Folder 10)
    - United Aircraft (Box 13:, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 13:, Folder 12)
    - University commercials (Box 13:, Folder 13)
    - University Scholars (Box 13:, Folder 14)
    - University secondary school (Box 13:, Folder 15)
    - University Senate (Box 13:, Folder 16)
    - V (Box 13:, Folder 17)
    - Van Bibber, E. George - Dir., School of Phys. Ed. (Box 13:, Folder 18)
    - W (Box 13:, Folder 19)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 13:, Folder 20)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 13:, Folder 21)
    - We (Box 13:, Folder 22)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean of the Graduate School (Box 13:, Folder 23)
    - Wi (Box 13:, Folder 24)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean of the School of Nursing (Box 13:, Folder 25)
    - Wo (Box 13:, Folder 26)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 13:, Folder 27)
    - Young, W. B. - Dean and Director, College of Agriculture (Box 13:, Folder 28)
    - Z (Box 13:, Folder 29)
  - 1956-1957
    - A (Box 13:, Folder 30)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean of Bus. Administration (Box 13:, Folder 31)
    - Administrative report (Box 13:, Folder 32)
    - Air Force (Box 13:, Folder 33)
    - American Council on Education (Box 13:, Folder 34)
    - Architects (Box 13:, Folder 35)
    - Army, Department of (Box 13:, Folder 36)
    - Attorney General (state) (Box 13:, Folder 37)
    - B (Box 13:, Folder 38)
    - Belden, L. Richard (Trustee) (Box 13:, Folder 39)
    - Bequests (Box 13:, Folder 40)
    - Bishop, Merlin (Trustee), 1956-1957 (Box 13:, Folder 41)
    - Board material (Box 13:, Folder 42)
    - Brammell, P. Roy - Dean, School of Education (Box 13:, Folder 43)
    - Brock, C. Ray (Trustee) (Box 13:, Folder 44)
    - Budget (Box 13:, Folder 45)
    - Budget division (state) (Box 13:, Folder 46)
    - C (Box 14:, Folder 1)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - Dean, College of Arts and Sciences (Box 14:, Folder 2)
    - Ce (Box 14:, Folder 3)
    - Christian, J. O. - Dir. Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 14:, Folder 4)
    - Co (Box 14:, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's housing (Box 14:, Folder 6)
    - College entrance examination board (Box 14:, Folder 7)
    - Commencement (Box 14:, Folder 8)
    - Committee letters (Box 14:, Folder 9)
    - Committee reports (Box 14:, Folder 10)
    - Conferences - Carlson E. Crane, Acting co - director Ext. S. S. and C.E. (Box 14:, Folder 11)
    - Congress (Box 14:, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut Advisory Committee on Food and Drugs (Box 14:, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut Citizens for the Public Schools (Box 14:, Folder 14)
    - Contracts (Box 14:, Folder 15)
    - Cr (Box 14:, Folder 16)
    - Deans and directors (Box 14:, Folder 17)
    - E (Box 14:, Folder 18)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 14:, Folder 19)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 14:, Folder 20)
    - Enrollment figures (Box 14:, Folder 21)
    - Fees, University (Box 14:, Folder 22)
    - Fi (Box 14:, Folder 23)
    - Finance commissioner - Joseph M. Loughlin (Box 14:, Folder 24)
    - Fitzgerald, William B. (Trustee) (Box 14:, Folder 25)
    - Fo (Box 14:, Folder 26)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 14:, Folder 27)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 14:, Folder 28)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 14:, Folder 29)
    - G (Box 14:, Folder 30)
    - Gerontology, Institutes of - Donald P. Kent, dir. (Box 14:, Folder 31)
    - Gill, Joseph N. - Commissioner of Agriculture (Box 14:, Folder 32)
    - Gleason, John H. - Director, Division of Communications (Box 14:, Folder 33)
    - Goodchild, Franklin M., M.D. - Director, Division of University Health (Box 14:, Folder 34)
    - Governor of Connecticut (Box 14:, Folder 35)
    - Grange Sunday (12 May 1957), 1956 - 1957 (Box 14:, Folder 36)
    - H (Box 14:, Folder 37)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 14:, Folder 38)
    - Hi (Box 14:, Folder 39)
    - Ho (Box 14:, Folder 40)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 14:, Folder 41)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency - Community Facilities Activities (Box 14:, Folder 42)
    - Husky Network (Box 14:, Folder 43)
    - I (Box 14:, Folder 44)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 14:, Folder 45)
    - J (Box 14:, Folder 46)
    - Joint Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs (Box 14:, Folder 47)
    - Ki (Box 14:, Folder 48)
    - L (Box 14:, Folder 49)
    - Legislative (Box 14:, Folder 50)
    - Legislative letters (Box 14:, Folder 51)
    - Liaison Committee (Box 14:, Folder 52)
    - Luncheon for Parents (Box 14:, Folder 53)
    - Mackie, Helen (Trustee) (Box 14:, Folder 54)
    - Mahoney, Mary (Trustee) (Box 14:, Folder 55)
    - Manning, Stuart—Acting co - director, University Extension, Summer Session and Continuing Education (Box 14:, Folder 56)
    - Map (Box 14:, Folder 57)
    - Marine Biology Laboratory (Box 14:, Folder 58)
    - Marsh, E. Lea, Jr. (Trustee) (Box 14:, Folder 59)
    - Marx, Henry (Box 14:, Folder 60)
    - May, Elizabeth E.—Dean, School of Home Economics (Box 14:, Folder 61)
    - McH (Box 14:, Folder 62)
    - McMahon, Brien—Letcure Series (Box 14:, Folder 63)
    - Medical - Dental (Box 14:, Folder 64)
    - Military day, 1957 May 16 (Box 14:, Folder 65)
    - Mitchell College - Robert C. Weller, President (Box 14:, Folder 66)
    - Mo (Box 14:, Folder 67)
    - N (Box 14:, Folder 68)
    - Naming of new buildings (Box 14:, Folder 69)
    - National Comm for Development of Scientists and Engineers - sixth meeting, June 12 (Box 14:, Folder 70)
    - National Education Association (Box 15:, Folder 1)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 15:, Folder 2)
    - New buildings (Box 15:, Folder 3)
    - Newburn, Harry - Educational Television and Radio Center (Box 15:, Folder 4)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 15:, Folder 5)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, 1956-1957 (Box 15:, Folder 6)
    - New England Board of Higher Education - Executive Committee, 1957 February 14 (Box 15:, Folder 7)
    - New England Land Grant Universities (Box 15:, Folder 8)
    - Northby, Arwood S. - Director of Student Personnel (Box 15:, Folder 9)
    - Nuclear reactor - H. P. Knauss, chr. (Box 15:, Folder 10)
    - O (Box 15:, Folder 11)
    - P (Box 15:, Folder 12)
    - Paul, George, Director, Labor Management Institute (Box 15:, Folder 13)
    - P1 (Box 15:, Folder 14)
    - Powers, John, Placement Officer (Box 15:, Folder 15)
    - President's Committee on Education beyond High School (Box 15:, Folder 16)
    - Public Works Department (Box 15:, Folder 17)
    - Re (Box 15:, Folder 18)
    - Real Estate (Box 15:, Folder 19)
    - Research Foundation (Box 15:, Folder 20)
    - Research grants (Box 15:, Folder 21)
    - Riccio, Leonard C - University Comptroller (Box 15:, Folder 22)
    - Ro (Box 15:, Folder 23)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 15:, Folder 24)
    - S (Box 15:, Folder 25)
    - Sanders, William - Commissioner of Education (Box 15:, Folder 26)
    - Sch (Box 15:, Folder 27)
    - Schneller, Richard (Trustee) (Box 15:, Folder 28)
    - Science talent (Box 15:, Folder 29)
    - Se (Box 15:, Folder 30)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (trustee, chairman) (Box 15:, Folder 31)
    - Sistare, Willard M. - Manager, University Auditorium (Box 15:, Folder 32)
    - Sm (Box 15:, Folder 33)
    - Speeches (Box 15:, Folder 34)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 15:, Folder 35)
    - State Building Program Commission (Box 15:, Folder 36)
    - State Universities Association (Box 15:, Folder 37)
    - Student Senate (Box 15:, Folder 38)
    - Summer meeting, New England Land Grant Presidents -, 1957 Jul 11 - 13 (Box 15:, Folder 39)
    - St (Box 15:, Folder 40)
    - Su (Box 15:, Folder 41)
    - T (Box 15:, Folder 42)
    - Tappen, Frances - Technical Dir. School of Physical Therapy (Box 15:, Folder 43)
    - Telephones (Box 15:, Folder 44)
    - TV (Box 15:, Folder 45)
    - TV Closed circuits - New York University (Box 15:, Folder 46)
    - To, 1956-1957 (Box 15:, Folder 47)
    - Torrington meeting -, 1956 August 16 (Box 15:, Folder 48)
    - Trecker, Harleigh - Dean, School of Social Work (Box 15:, Folder 49)
    - Union board and building - Max Andrews, manager (Box 15:, Folder 50)
    - United Aircraft (Box 15:, Folder 51)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 15:, Folder 52)
    - University scholars (Box 15:, Folder 53)
    - University secondary school (Box 15:, Folder 54)
    - University Senate (Box 15:, Folder 55)
    - V (Box 15:, Folder 56)
    - Van Bibber, E. George - Dir. School of Phys. Ed. (Box 15:, Folder 57)
    - Vo - Ag Center (Box 15:, Folder 58)
    - W (Box 15:, Folder 59)
    - Waterbury (parking) (Box 15:, Folder 60)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 15:, Folder 61)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 15:, Folder 62)
    - We (Box 15:, Folder 63)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean of the Graduate School (Box 15:, Folder 64)
    - Wi (Box 15:, Folder 65)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 15:, Folder 66)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 15:, Folder 67)
    - Young, Wilfred B. - Dean, College of Agriculture (Box 15:, Folder 68)
  - 1957-1958
    - A (Box 15:, Folder 69)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean of School of Bus. Admin. (Box 15:, Folder 70)
    - Administrative report (Box 15:, Folder 71)
    - Advisers (Box 15:, Folder 72)
    - Air Force (Box 15:, Folder 73)
    - Alcorn, Paul, Director, Wilbur Cross Library (Box 15:, Folder 74)
    - Alumni (Box 15:, Folder 75)
    - American Council on Education (Box 15:, Folder 76)
    - An (Box 15:, Folder 77)
    - Architects (Box 15:, Folder 78)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 15:, Folder 79)
    - Attorney General (Box 15:, Folder 80)
    - B (Box 16:, Folder 1)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 2)
    - Bequests (Box 16:, Folder 3)
    - Bi (Box 16:, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Data (Box 16:, Folder 5)
    - Bishop, Merlin (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 6)
    - Bo, 1957-1958 (Box 16:, Folder 7)
    - Board material (Box 16:, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees, Special Finance Committee J. Raymond Brock, Chair (Box 16:, Folder 9)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 16:, Folder 10)
    - Brammell, P. Roy - Dean, School of Education (Box 16:, Folder 11)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 12)
    - Budget (Box 16:, Folder 13)
    - Business Administration School Building (Box 16:, Folder 14)
    - C (Box 16:, Folder 15)
    - Campus - Steve Jones, Editor (Box 16:, Folder 16)
    - Capital projects (Box 16:, Folder 17)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - Dean, College of Arts and Sciences (Box 16:, Folder 18)
    - Crane, Carl (Box 16:, Folder 19)
    - Ce (Box 16:, Folder 20)
    - Christian, J. O. - Director of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 16:, Folder 21)
    - Civil Defense (Box 16:, Folder 22)
    - Co (Box 16:, Folder 23)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's housing (Box 16:, Folder 24)
    - Committee letters (Box 16:, Folder 25)
    - Committee reports (Box 16:, Folder 26)
    - Commencement (Box 16:, Folder 27)
    - Congress (Box 16:, Folder 28)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 16:, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut Food Stores Assoc., Inc. (Box 16:, Folder 30)
    - Construction in process (Box 16:, Folder 31)
    - Contracts (Box 16:, Folder 32)
    - Coo (Box 16:, Folder 33)
    - Deans and directors (Box 16:, Folder 34)
    - Do (Box 16:, Folder 35)
    - Donahue, Alphonsus J., Jr. (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 36)
    - Dormitories (Box 16:, Folder 37)
    - Dr (Box 16:, Folder 38)
    - E (Box 16:, Folder 39)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 16:, Folder 40)
    - Eisenbach, Rabbi (Box 16:, Folder 41)
    - En (Box 16:, Folder 42)
    - Fees, University (Box 16:, Folder 43)
    - Finance and Control, Department of - George J. Conkling, Commissioner (Box 16:, Folder 44)
    - Financial statement (Box 16:, Folder 45)
    - Fine Arts building (Box 16:, Folder 46)
    - Fitzgerald, William B. (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 47)
    - Ge, 1957-1958 (Box 16:, Folder 48)
    - Gill, Joseph N. - Commissioner of Agriculture (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 49)
    - Gleason, John H. - Director of Communications (Box 16:, Folder 50)
    - Goodchild, F. M. - Director, University Health (Box 16:, Folder 51)
    - Governor of Connecticut - Abraham A. Ribicoff (Box 16:, Folder 52)
    - Gr (Box 16:, Folder 53)
    - Grievance (Box 16:, Folder 54)
    - H (Box 16:, Folder 55)
    - Har (Box 16:, Folder 56)
    - Hartford Branch - Wilbur R. Griswold, Supervisor (Box 16:, Folder 57)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 16:, Folder 58)
    - Hi (Box 16:, Folder 59)
    - Ho (Box 16:, Folder 60)
    - Honors Day, 1950 May 18 (Box 16:, Folder 61)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 16:, Folder 62)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 16:, Folder 63)
    - Hu (Box 16:, Folder 64)
    - I (Box 16:, Folder 65)
    - Institutes of Gerontology - Donald P. Kent (Box 16:, Folder 66)
    - Institute of Marine Research, The - John S. Rankin, Director (Box 16:, Folder 67)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 16:, Folder 68)
    - Institute for Secondary School Teachers of Physics (Box 16:, Folder 69)
    - Insurance (Box 16:, Folder 70)